Contact

8305624838 (Mobile) amandewatnitrr@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/aman-kumar-dewangan-akd13o1 (LinkedIn) github.com/amandewatnitrr (Personal) amandewatnitrr2020.blogspot..com (Blog) medium.com/@amandewatnitrr (Blog)

Top Skills

Arduino

Internet of Things (IoT)

C++

Languages

Hindi (Elementary)

English (Elementary)

Chhattisgarhi (Limited Working)

Certifications

MongoDB Basics

Interfacing with the Arduino

Python for Beginners

HackCoVIT

Epidemics, Pandemics and Outbreaks

Honors-Awards

ROBOTHON_1.0 - 2nd position

2nd Position - Innovation in Isolation

Publications

Application of IoT and Machine Learning in Agriculture

TECHNOLOGY INFLUENCING DISASTER MANAGEMENT

Aman Kumar Dewangan

Electrical Undergrad at NIT Raipur || IoT, Robotics & Automation Enthusiast || Frontend Developer || Embedded System Raipur

Summary

Currently pursuing B.Tech in Electrical Engineering from National Institute of Technology Raipur. My Personal Area of Intrest belongs to IoT ad Hardwar Development using Raspberry Pi and Arduino. I also like Content Writting and pursue it as my hobby.

For any research purpose or project collaboration feel free to contact me anytime.

Only Paid Work.

Experience

IEEE Bombay Section
Chairman of Documentation Committee
August 2020 - Present (1 month)
Raipur, Chhattisgarh, India

Naipui, Ciliattisgairi, Iriula

Innovation Cell, NIT Raipur

1 year 1 month

Technical Coordinator January 2020 - Present (8 months)

NIT RAIPUR

Documentation Executive August 2019 - Present (1 year 1 month)

NiT RAIPUR, Chhattisgarh

Technical Executive August 2019 - January 2020 (6 months)

Nit Raipur, Chhattisgarh

Tech4gud Society

Member

June 2020 - Present (3 months)

Page 1 of 2

National Institute of Technology, Andhra Pradesh Summer Research Intern May 2020 - August 2020 (4 months)

Kriyative Education
Content Writer
April 2020 - June 2020 (3 months)
Technical Content Writer

IEEE Student Branch NIT Raipur 1 year

Documentation Executive April 2019 - March 2020 (1 year) Raipur, Chhattisgarh

Executive Event Manager April 2019 - March 2020 (1 year) Raipur, Chattisgarh, India

Education

National Institute of Technology Raipur
Bachelor of Technology, Electrical Engineering (2018 - 2022)

All India Society for Electronics and Computer Technology High School Diploma, Computer Application · (2019 - 2020)

Krishna Public School Raipur 12th, PCM · (2017 - 2018)